[{"question": " hey gorgeous, how's it going?", "answer": " dehydrated japanese noodles under fluorescent lights... does it get better than this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " question. you're not dating anybody, are you, because i met somebody who would be perfect for you.", "answer": " ah, y'see, perfect might be a problem. had you said 'co-dependent', or 'self-destructive'...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " do you want a date saturday?", "answer": " yes please.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " okay. he's cute, he's funny, he's-", "answer": " he's a he?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " ...couldn't enjoy a cup of noodles after that. i mean, is that ridiculous? can you believe she actually thought that?", "answer": " um... yeah. well, i mean, when i first met you, y'know, i thought maybe, possibly, you might be...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " you did?", "answer": " yeah, but then you spent phoebe's entire birthday party talking to my breasts, so then i figured maybe not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " huh. did, uh... any of the rest of you guys think that when you first met me?", "answer": " i did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " yeah, i think so, yeah.", "answer": " not me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " nono, me neither. although, uh, y'know, back in college, susan sallidor did.", "answer": " you're kidding! did you tell her i wasn't?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " well, this is fascinating. so, uh, what is it about me?", "answer": " i dunno, 'cause you're smart, you're funny...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " ross is smart and funny, d'you ever think that about him?", "answer": " yeah! right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " what is it?!", "answer": " okay, i-i d'know, you-you just- you have a quality.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " yes. absolutely. a quality.", "answer": " oh, oh, a quality, good, because i was worried you guys were gonna be vague about this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " hello? hello? oh! rachel, it's paolo calling from rome.", "answer": " oh my god! calling from rome!  bon giorno, caro mio.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": "  so he's calling from rome. i could do that. just gotta go to rome.", "answer": " monica, your dad just beeped in, but can you make it quick? talking to rome.  i'm talking to rome.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " so, uh, how's she doing?", "answer": " the doctor says it's a matter of hours.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " how-how are you, mom?", "answer": " me? i'm fine, fine. i'm glad you're here. ...what's with your hair?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " what's different?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " nothing.", "answer": " oh, maybe that's it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " she is unbelievable, our mother is...", "answer": " okay, relax, relax. we are gonna be here for a while, it looks like, and we still have boyfriends and your career to cover.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " the fuzzy little mints at the bottom of her purse.", "answer": " oh! ...yeah, they were gross. oh, you know what i loved? her sweet 'n' los. how she was always stealing them from- from restaurants.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " she looks so small.", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " well, at least she's with pop-pop and aunt phyllis now.", "answer": " g'bye, nana.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " what is going on?!", "answer": " y'know how-how the nurse said that-that nana had passed? well, she's not, quite..", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " she's not- past, she's present, she's back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": "  what's going on?", "answer": " she may have died.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " she may have died?", "answer": " we're looking into it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " i just have to know, okay. is it my hair?", "answer": "  yes, chandler, that's exactly what it is. it's your hair.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " so, um, did she...", "answer": " twice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " twice?", "answer": " oh, that sucks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " you guys okay?", "answer": " i dunno, it's weird. i mean, i know she's gone, but i just don't feel, uh...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " maybe that's 'cause she's not really gone.", "answer": " nono, she's gone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " we checked. a lot.", "answer": " hm, i mean maybe no-one ever really goes. ever since my mom died, every now and then, i get the feeling that she's like right here, y'know?  oh! and debbie, my best friend from junior high- got struck by lightning on a miniature golf course- i always get this really strong debbie vibe whenever i use one of those little yellow pencils, y'know? ...i miss her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " thanks!", "answer": " sure. i just sharpened her this morning.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " now, see, i don't believe any of that. i think once you're dead, you're dead! you're gone! you're worm food!  ...so chandler looks gay, huh?", "answer": " y'know, i dunno who this is, but it's not debbie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " i thought it was gonna be a closed casket.", "answer": " well, that doesn't mean she can't look nice!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " sweetie, you think you can get in there?", "answer": "  i don't see why not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " i was just thinking. when my time comes-", "answer": " dad!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " listen to me! when my time comes, i wanna be buried at sea.", "answer": " you what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " i wanna be buried at sea, it looks like fun.", "answer": " define fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " c'mon, you'll make a day of it! you'll rent a boat, pack a lunch...", "answer": " ...and then we throw your body in the water... gee, that does sound fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " everyone thinks they know me. everyone says 'jack geller, so predictable'. maybe after i'm gone, they'll say 'buried at sea! huh!'.", "answer": " that's probably what they'll say.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " hey, gorgeous.", "answer": "  hey. look, i'm sorry about yesterday, i, um-", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " no, nono, don't- don't worry about it. believe me, apparently other people have made the same mistake.", "answer": " oh! okay! phew!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " so, uh... what do you think it is about me?", "answer": " i dunno, uh... you just have a-a...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " ...quality, right, great.", "answer": " y'know, it's a shame, because you and lowell would've made a great couple.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " lowell? financial services' lowell, that's who you saw me with?", "answer": " what? he's cute!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " well, yeah... 's'no brian in payroll.", "answer": " is brian...?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " no! uh, i d'know! the point is, if you were gonna set me up with someone, i'd like to think you'd set me up with someone like him.", "answer": " well, i think brian's a little out of your league.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": "  this one?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " i have shown you everything we have. unless you want your mother to spend eternity in a lemon yellow pant-suit, go with the burgundy.", "answer": " you know, whatever we pick, she would've told us it's the wrong one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " you're right. we'll go with the burgundy.", "answer": " oh! a fine choice. i'm coming out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " that's really a day shoe.", "answer": " and where she's going everyone else'll be dressier?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " could we see something in a slimmer heel?", "answer": "  okay, i have nothing in an evening shoe in the burgundy. i can show you something in a silver that may work.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " no, it really should be burgundy.", "answer": " mm. unless we go with a different dress?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " oh my god..", "answer": " is everything all right, dear?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": "  how we doing, you guys ready?", "answer": " mom already called this morning to remind me not to wear my hair up. did you know my ears are not my best feature?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " some days it's all i can think about.", "answer": "  hi, sorry i'm late, i couldn't find my bearings.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " oh, you-you mean your earrings?", "answer": " what'd i say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " hm-m.", "answer": " are these the shoes?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " yes. paolo sent them from italy.", "answer": " what, we-uh- we don't have shoes here, or...?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": "  morning. we ready to go?", "answer": " well, don't we look nice all dressed up?...it's stuff like that, isn't it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " it was a really beautiful service.", "answer": " it really was. oh, c'mere, sweetheart.  y'know, i think it might be time for you to start using night cream.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " nothing, just your overcoat sounds remarkably like brent mussberger.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " you're watching a football game at a funeral?", "answer": " no, it's the pre-game. i'm gonna watch it at the reception.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " oh no! my new paolo shoes!", "answer": " oh, i hope they're not ruined.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " god, what a great day. ...what? weather-wise!", "answer": " i know, uh, the air, the-the trees... even though nana's gone there's, there's something almost, uh- i dunno, almost life-aff-", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " god! ross!", "answer": " i'm fine. just-just... having my worst fear realised...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " okay, don't worry, i'm just checking to see if the muscle's in spasm...huh.", "answer": " what, what is it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " you missed a belt loop.", "answer": " oh! no-n-", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " okay, it's in spasm.", "answer": " here, sweetie, here. i took these when i had my golfing accident.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " oh, no-", "answer": " sorry- hi, i'm dorothy's daughter.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " hey, look who's up! how do you feel?", "answer": " i feel great. i feel- great, i fleel great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " wow, those pills really worked, huh?", "answer": " not the first two, but the second two- woooo! ...i love you guys. you guys are the greatest. i love my sister , i love pheebs..", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " ooh! that's so nice...", "answer": " ...chandler!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": "  and listen, man, if you wanna be gay, be gay. doesn't matter to me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " rachel. rachel rachel.  i love you the most.", "answer": "  oh, well you know who i love the most?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " whaddya got there?", "answer": "  just a, uh... hearing disability.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " what's the score?", "answer": " seventeen-fourteen giants... three minutes to go in the third.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": "  pheebs, could you maybe hand me a cracker?", "answer": "  your grandmother would have hated this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " well, sure, what with it being her funeral and all.", "answer": " no, i'd be hearing about 'why didn't i get the honey-glazed ham?', i didn't spend enough on flowers, and if i spent more she'd be saying 'why are you wasting your money? i don't need flowers, i'm dead'.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " that sounds like nana.", "answer": " do you know what it's like to grow up with someone who is critical of every single thing you say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " ...i can imagine.", "answer": " i'm telling you, it's a wonder your mother turned out to be the positive, life-affirming person that she is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " that is a wonder. so tell me something, mom. if you had to do it all over again, i mean, if she was here right now, would you tell her?", "answer": " tell her what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " how she drove you crazy, picking on every little detail, like your hair... for example.", "answer": " i'm not sure i know what you're getting at.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " do you think things would have been better if you'd just told her the truth?", "answer": " ...no. i think some things are better left unsaid. i think it's nicer when people just get along.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " huh.", "answer": " more wine, dear?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " oh, i think so.", "answer": "  those earrings look really lovely on you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " thank you. they're yours.", "answer": " actually they were nana's.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " hey, who's this little naked guy?", "answer": " that little naked guy would be me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " aww, look at the little thing.", "answer": " yes, yes, fine, that is my penis. can we be grown-ups now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " who are those people?", "answer": " got me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " oh, that's nana, right there in the middle.  'me and the gang at java joe's'.", "answer": " wow, monica, you look just like your grandmother. how old was she there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " let's see, 1939... yeah, 24, 25?", "answer": " looks like a fun gang.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " ooh, look look look look look! i got monica naked!", "answer": "  nono, that would be me again. i'm, uh, just trying something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " hey, lowell.", "answer": " hey, chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " so how's it going there in financial services?", "answer": " it's like mardi gras without the paper mache heads. how 'bout you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " good, good. listen, heh, i dunno what shelley told you about me, but, uh... i'm not.", "answer": " i know. that's what i told her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " really.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " so- you can tell?", "answer": " pretty much, most of the time. we have a kind of... radar.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " so you don't think i have a, a quality?", "answer": " speaking for my people, i'd have to say no. by the way, your friend brian from payroll, he is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " he is?", "answer": " yup, and waaay out of your league.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}]